[
    {
        "Question": "What is Launcher?",
        "Answer Given": "request-based method",
        "Score": 0.48886051774024963,
        "Actual Answer": "a framework for running large collections of serial multithreaded applications known as High Throughput Computing (HTC)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How can users submit Launcher jobs?",
        "Answer Given": "by creating a SLURM job script",
        "Score": 0.4881553649902344,
        "Actual Answer": "by creating a SLURM job script"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many tasks can be ran in a job?",
        "Answer Given": "16",
        "Score": 0.6988314986228943,
        "Actual Answer": "16 - 60"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are two useful parameters?",
        "Answer Given": "$LAUNCHER_JID and $LAUNCHER_TSK_ID",
        "Score": 0.931394100189209,
        "Actual Answer": "$LAUNCHER_JID and $LAUNCHER_TSK_ID"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What can I not use Launcher for?",
        "Answer Given": "run Matlab, ANSYS, or Mathematica jobs in parallel",
        "Score": 0.06175381690263748,
        "Actual Answer": "Matlab, ANSYS, or Mathematica jobs in parallel"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is $LAUNCHER_JID?",
        "Answer Given": "the rank of the jobs listed in the job file",
        "Score": 0.6596297025680542,
        "Actual Answer": "the rank of the jobs listed in the job file"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does Launcher not support?",
        "Answer Given": "MPI jobs",
        "Score": 0.8911303281784058,
        "Actual Answer": "MPI jobs"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Launcher not used for?",
        "Answer Given": "MPI jobs",
        "Score": 0.34143829345703125,
        "Actual Answer": "Matlab, ANSYS, or Mathematica jobs in parallel"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the name of the newly developed tool based on Launcher?",
        "Answer Given": "Launcher-GPU",
        "Score": 0.7915759682655334,
        "Actual Answer": "Launcher-GPU"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does $LAUNCHER_TSK_ID?",
        "Answer Given": "the rank of the tasks (-n) running simultaneously",
        "Score": 0.6239954233169556,
        "Actual Answer": "the rank of the tasks (-n) running simultaneously"
    }
]